https://swarb.co.uk/privacy-users/

Skip to content
Save as set out below, we do not allow comments, or the uploading of images, or registration of users. We collect no information about individual users, and therefore have no personal information as to users to protect, remove, disclose or delete.
We do invite donations. Donations are mediated through PayPal, who may inform us of your email address and name and contribution, but not further.
We do not carry social network buttons allowing those networks to track your activity here.
We use Google Analytics and a WordPress plugin called Jetpack to collect record, and retain the IP address of a visitor and the web pages requested. An IP address might sometimes, in principle, allow the identification of the machine from the page request originated.
This data allows us to identify which pages are most visited, and are worthy of or require further noting up, and to promote the site to attract advertising.
Google analytics bases its analysis on the URL of the page visited, together with the IP address of the browser calling it. Our URLs do not include any additional information. Google asseses a broad geolocation for the location of the browser, but does not seek to identify a user (you). Google Analytics has its privacy policy.
We do retain statistics about the use of the site, but not in a way which comprises data about individual users.
Our web-hosting is provided by 34sp of Manchester. Necessarily, they log IP addresses of visitors. Their privacy policy is provides (at May 2018): “We collect the IP address of anyone visiting your website and store it in your site’s access logs. We use this IP address to track attacks on websites we host and allow us take steps to prevent those attacks. We keep access logs for 28 days on Professional Hosting and 30 days on Universal and Business Hosting.”
Wordpress’ Jetpack is provided by Automattic their privacy policy is available from the link. See Also Jetpack Privacy
Paypal has a privacy policy
Search for:
Buy Me a Coffee
Areas of Law:
Administrative (1,052)
Adoption (404)
Agency (595)
Agriculture (746)
Animals (282)
Arbitration (1,165)
Armed Forces (341)
Banking (1,353)
Benefits (3,410)
Capital Gains Tax (447)
Charity (371)
Child Support (299)
Children (4,870)
Civil Procedure Rules (364)
Commercial (1,343)
Commonwealth (3,069)
Company (2,847)
Constitutional (930)
Construction (1,136)
Consumer (688)
Contempt of Court (974)
Contract (5,852)
Coroners (387)
Corporation Tax (614)
Costs (3,313)
Crime (7,793)
Criminal Evidence (616)
Criminal Practice (3,158)
Criminal Sentencing (3,018)
Customs and Excise (1,570)
Damages (2,448)
Defamation (1,471)
Development (2)
Discrimination (2,634)
Ecclesiastical (296)
Education (990)
Elections (213)
Employment (14,374)
Environment (763)
Equity (943)
Estoppel (322)
European (12,769)
Evidence (486)
Extradition (1,328)
Family (2,704)
Financial Services (962)
Health (1,363)
Health and Safety (454)
Health Professions (1,755)
Housing (1,962)
Human Rights (17,192)
Immigration (72,192)
Income Tax (2,902)
Information (13,967)
Inheritance Tax (171)
Insolvency (2,850)
Insurance (1,207)
Intellectual Property (15,774)
International (914)
Ireland (18)
Judicial Review (576)
Jurisdiction (958)
Jury (3,562)
Land (5,065)
Landlord and Tenant (15,743)
Legal Aid (379)
Legal Professions (1,891)
Licensing (554)
Limitation (1,041)
Litigation Practice (6,763)
Local Governent (1)
Local Government (1,523)
Magistrates (703)
Media (1,094)
Natural Justice (322)
Negligence (1,338)
News (49)
Northern Ireland (2,931)
Nuisance (458)
Personal Injury (2,942)
Planning (2,936)
Police (1,503)
Prisons (1,131)
Professional Negligence (1,623)
Rating (634)
Registered Land (798)
Road Traffic (1,172)
Scotland (16,728)
Stamp Duty (143)
Taxes – Other (2,161)
Taxes Management (1,144)
Torts – Other (2,602)
Transport (1,885)
Trusts (1,382)
Undue Influence (156)
Utilities (437)
VAT (5,029)
Vicarious Liability (244)
Wales (15)
Wills and Probate (1,594)
Recent Posts
The Queen v Secretary of State for the Home Department, ex parte Barkoci and Malik and similar: ECJ 27 Sep 2001
Regina v Looseley (orse Loosely); Attorney General’s Reference No 3 of 2000: HL 25 Oct 2001
Loutchansky v The Times Newspapers Ltd and Others (Nos 2 to 5): CA 5 Dec 2001
Regina (on the Application of Pretty) v Director of Public Prosecutions and Secretary of State for the Home Department: HL 29 Nov 2001
MP (a Child) v Mid-Kent Healthcare Trust: CA 5 Nov 2001
Paragon Finance plc v Nash etc: CA 15 Oct 2001
Director General of Fair Trading v First National Bank: HL 25 Oct 2001
Farley v Skinner: HL 11 Oct 2001
Chief Constable of West Yorkshire Police v Khan: HL 11 Oct 2001
Secretary of State for the Home Department v Rehman: HL 11 Oct 2001
B v The United Kingdom; P v The United Kingdom: ECHR 24 Apr 2001
V v The United Kingdom; T v The United Kingdom: ECHR 16 Dec 1999
Royal Bank of Scotland v Etridge (No 2); Barclays Bank plc v Harris; Midland Bank plc v Wallace, etc: HL 11 Oct 2001
Uratemp Ventures Limited v Collins: HL 11 Oct 2001
Regina v Shayler: CACD 28 Sep 2001
Three Rivers District Council and Others v Governor and Company of The Bank of England (No 3): HL 23 Mar 2001
Regina v Savage; Director of Public Prosecutions v Parmenter: HL 7 Nov 1991
Jordan v United Kingdom; McKerr v United Kingdom; similar: ECHR 4 May 2001
Bensaid v The United Kingdom: ECHR 6 Feb 2001
Thlimmenos v Greece: ECHR 6 Apr 2000
McGonnell v The United Kingdom: ECHR 8 Feb 2000
Soderback v Sweden: ECHR 28 Oct 1998
Fressoz and Roire v France: ECHR 21 Jan 1999
Osman v The United Kingdom: ECHR 28 Oct 1998
Halford v The United Kingdom: ECHR 25 Jun 1997
Z v Finland: ECHR 25 Feb 1997
Gregory v The United Kingdom: ECHR 25 Feb 1997
Aksoy v Turkey: ECHR 18 Dec 1996
Chahal v The United Kingdom: ECHR 15 Nov 1996
Saunders v The United Kingdom: ECHR 17 Dec 1996
The Sunday Times (No 1) v The United Kingdom: ECHR 26 Apr 1979
Brannigan and McBride v The United Kingdom: ECHR 26 May 1993
Goodwin v The United Kingdom: ECHR 27 Mar 1996
SW v The United Kingdom; CR v United Kingdom: ECHR 22 Nov 1995
Otto-Preminger-Institut v Austria: ECHR 20 Sep 1994
Kokkinakis v Greece: ECHR 25 May 1993
Drozd and Janousek v France and Spain: ECHR 26 Jun 1992
The Sunday Times v The United Kingdom (No 2): ECHR 26 Nov 1991
Soering v The United Kingdom: ECHR 7 Jul 1989
Kostovski v The Netherlands: ECHR 20 Nov 1989
Weeks v The United Kingdom: ECHR 5 Oct 1988
Abdulaziz etc v The United Kingdom: ECHR 28 May 1985
James and Others v The United Kingdom: ECHR 21 Feb 1986
Sporrong and Lonnroth v Sweden: ECHR 18 Dec 1984
X and Y v The Netherlands: ECHR 26 Mar 1985
Ashingdane v The United Kingdom: ECHR 28 May 1985
WordPress.org
swarb.co.uk is published by David Swarbrick of 10 Halifax Road, Brighouse West Yorkshire HD6 2AG. Tel: 0795 457 9992, 01484 380326 or email at david@swarb.co.uk
IMPORTANT:This site reports and summarizes cases. We do not provide advice. Before making any decision, you must read the full case report and take professional advice as appropriate. Only full case reports are accepted in court.
This site uses cookies to improve your experience. Read more.No problem
